poetsandquants.com 2019-09-19

# Privacy Policy | Poets&Quants

This Privacy Policy governs your use of this web site and all sites controlled or hosted by C-Change Media, including but not limited to [ **www.poetsandquants.com**](http://www.poetsandquants.com/),  [**www.poetsandquantsforexecs.com**](http://www.poetsandquantsforexecs.com/),  [**www.poetsandquantsforundergrads.com**](http://www.poetsandquantsforundergrads.com/),  [**www.tippingthescales.com**](http://www.tippingthescales.com/),  and  [**www.weseegenius.com**](http://www.weseegenius.com/) (collectively the “Site” or “Sites”), which is made available by C-Change Media. This Privacy Policy also applies to all mobile applications controlled or operated by C-Change Media.

This Privacy Policy outlines the type of Personal Information and other information that is collected through one or all of the Sites and how that information is used and protected.

  * Your Consent to this Privacy Policy
  * Personal Information
  * Right to Opt-In and Opt-Out
  * Information Collected on this Web Site
  * How Personal Information is Used
  * Security
  * Information for Residents of the EEA
  * Changes to this Privacy Policy
  * Contact Us

**Your Consent to this Privacy Policy**

By visiting this Site, and/or using the services offered on or through this Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy as they may be amended from time to time. As we update and expand the Site’s Terms of Use, this Privacy Policy may change, so check back to this page from time to time. The term “Site” is deemed to include accessing or using the Site by means of a computer, a mobile device or a mobile application and applies to all users or visitors of our Site. By providing Personal Information to this Web Site, you understand and consent to the collection, maintenance, processing and transfer of such information in and to the United States and other countries and territories, in accordance with United States law.

**Personal Information**

We may from time to time ask you for Personal Information, and we may collect certain information from your computer each time you visit our Site. “Personal Information” means personally identifiable information and may include, for example, your name; street address; e-mail address; SMS or text message address; phone number; credit card and other payment information; information that you choose to provide regarding your academic and extracurricular activities and interests that may identify you; and/or other information that may identify you as an individual or allow online contact with you.

**Right to Opt-In and Opt-Out**

You have the right to “opt-in” and “opt-out” of certain of our uses of your Personal Information. If you no longer wish to receive any marketing communications from us, you may request to be removed from our email list. You may send an e-mail to [ **Privacy@PoetsandQuants.com**](mailto:heather@poetsandquants.com) requesting removal from the Site’s email distribution list to opt-out from our marketing communication and delete your registered user account on the Site. You may also do this by unsubscribing to any email communication you receive from us.

Please understand that if you opt-out of receiving promotional correspondence from us, we may still contact you in connection with your relationship, activities, transactions and communications with us.

We may allow third-parties to display advertisements on our Site. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements. These third parties may collect information about whether you, or others who are using your computer, saw and/or clicked on the advertisements they deliver (such as click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over, etc.), and possibly associate this information with your subsequent visits to the advertised websites. Some of these third-party advertising companies may be advertising networks that are members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member companies and provides information about this behavioral advertising practice (  ** _[www.networkadvertising.org ](http://www.networkadvertising.org%20/)_**). You may opt out of our collection of data for use by third party ad companies to provide targeted advertising to you of our products as you visit other sites. Cookies are unique to each computer. Therefore, you must opt out separately on all computers you use. If you delete all of your cookies (specifically, the “Out-Out” cookie), you will have to go through the opt-out process again to reactivate your opted-out status.

You may opt out of tracking by Google Analytics by [clicking here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en-GB).

To see an overview of privacy at Google please [click here](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html).

**Information Collected on this Web Site**

**User-Provided Information**

We may collect Personal Information from users when they register or create an account on our Site, or through other ways such as through such user’s activities, transactions and completion of surveys or other similar types of canvassing and other online forms on our Site. We may use or disclose information provided by users in response to surveys or similar types of canvassing tools for purposes of promotions or other statements to third parties in a manner that does not personally identify any individual user.

**Web Site Usage Information**

  * We may use “cookies” to keep, and sometimes track, information about you, and to create a personalized Web experience. Cookies are small data files that are stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies track where you travel on our Site and what you look at and purchase. By using this Site, you agree to our use of cookies in this way. Most Web browsers can be set to inform you when a cookie has been sent to you and provide you with the opportunity to refuse that cookie. Additionally, if you have a Flash player installed on your computer, your Flash player can be set to reject or delete Flash cookies. However, refusing a cookie may, in some cases, preclude you from using, or negatively impact the display or function of, the Site or certain areas or features of the Site.
  * Our website also uses Google Analytics Cookies.  Information collected by the Google Analytics cookies will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States of America in accordance with its privacy practices.To see an overview of privacy at Google please [click here](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html). You may opt out of tracking by Google Analytics by [clicking here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en-GB). Otherwise, if you agree to our use of cookies, please continue to use our site.
  * Clear GIFs. We may use “clear GIFs” (a/k/a “Web beacons” or “pixel tags”) or similar technologies, on the Site and/or in our communications (e.g., in our HTML-based e-mails) which enable us to know whether you have visited a Web page or received or opened a message. This allows us to know the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.
  * IP Address and Clickstream Data. We automatically collect information from your browser when you visit our Site. This information includes your IP address, your browser type and language, access times, the content of any undeleted cookies that your browser previously accepted from us and the referring website address.

**How Personal Information is Used**

We may use your Personal Information to:

  * provide you with product and service offerings,
  * process requests and inquiries, including sharing your information as requested by you
  * maintain our internal record keeping and otherwise manage our business,
  * send you e-mail notices and offers and otherwise correspond with you, about products, services, companies and events that we think might interest you,
  * perform research and analysis about your use of or interest in our products, services or products or services offered by others,
  * develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests on our site and other sites,
  * provide advertisements to you when you visit other sites, and
  * perform other functions as which may be described to you at the time the personal information is collected.

**Service Providers**

We may share your Personal Information with vendors and other third parties who help deliver our products and services. These third parties are not authorized by us to use your Personal Information in any other way.

**Aggregated and non-Personal Information**

We may share non-Personal Information we collect under any of the above circumstances. We may also share it with other companies and third parties to develop and deliver targeted advertising on our websites and on websites of third parties, and to analyze and report on advertising you see. We may combine Site usage information we collect with other non-Personal Information we obtain from other sources. We also may share aggregated, non-Personal Information with third parties, including advisors, advertisers and investors, for the purpose of conducting general business analysis.

**Your Access Rights**

You may review and correct the Personal Information that is accessible to you in your user account on this Site by visiting the “My Profile” area of your account on any Site hosted by C-Change Media for which you are a registered user.

**Children’s Privacy**

You may only use the Site if you’re over the age at which you can provide consent to data processing under the laws of your country. Regardless of local laws, children under 13 aren’t allowed to use the Site. If you are a parent and you learn that your child is using the Site, and you don’t want them to, please get in touch with our [General Manager](mailto:heather@poetsandquants.com). Or email us at [Privacy@PoetsandQuants.com](mailto:Privacy@PoetsandQuants.com).

We do not verify and track parental consent – so unfortunately, if you’re below the age at which you can provide consent in your country, you aren’t entitled to use the Site.

**Third Party “Linked-To” Web Sites**

When you are on our Site you may be able to visit or link to other sites not operated by us. We do not control such sites and we are not responsible for the information practices of these sites. This Privacy Policy does not address the information practices of those other websites, and we encourage you to read the posted privacy policies of such sites.

**Legally Compelled Disclosures**

We may disclose user information when compelled to do so by government authorities or otherwise as required or permitted by law, such as to respond to court orders and subpoenas. We also may disclose user information when we have reason to believe that someone is causing injury to or interfering with our rights or property, other customers or users of the Site, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.

**Business Transfer**

In the event that C-Change Media, a portion of its business, or one or more of its divisions, is acquired by one or more third parties as a result of an acquisition, merger, sale, reorganization, consolidation or liquidation, Personal Information may be one of the transferred assets.

**Security**

When you contribute to a public area or feature of our Site, such as a chat room, bulletin board, list serve, blog, wiki or other open forum, the information that you submit will be made available to the public. Therefore, we recommend that you do not submit any sensitive information to such areas of our Site, including your full name, home address, phone number, financial information or any other information that would enable other users to locate you or contact you.

Users should also take care with how they handle and disclose their Personal Information and should avoid sending Personal Information through insecure email, SMS messaging or similar communications. Please refer to the Federal Trade Commission’s website at [ **http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/menus/consumer/data.shtm  **](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/menus/consumer/data.shtm)for information about how to protect yourself against identity theft.

**_Data Retention_**

We store the information we collect about you for as long as is necessary for the purpose(s) for which we originally collected it. We may retain certain information for legitimate business purposes or as required by law.

**_Data Transfers_**

To provide access to the Site, we may transfer your information to C-Change Media servers in the United States or other countries.  When we transfer information from the European Economic Area (“EEA”) to countries that have not been deemed to provide an adequate level of protection, we employ data processing agreements based on the Standard Contractual Clauses to help ensure that your data is protected wherever it is transferred. You may request a copy of these clauses by contacting us at Privacy@PoetsandQuants.com.

**Additional Information for Residents of the European Economic Area**

If you are a resident of the EEA, you have certain rights and protections under the law regarding the processing of your personal information.

**Legal Basis for Processing**

If you are a resident of the EEA, when we process your personal data we will only do so in the following situations:

  * We need to use your personal information to perform our responsibilities under our contract with you (e.g., providing services or content to you that you have requested).
  * We have a legitimate interest in processing your personal data. For example, we may process your personal data to send you marketing communications, to communicate with you about changes to the Site, and to provide, secure, and improve the services offered through the Site.

**  Data Subject Requests  **

If you are a resident of the EEA, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, erased, or transferred.  You may also have the right to object to, or request that we restrict, certain processing. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, you may contact us as indicated below.

**Questions or Complaints**

If you are a resident of the EEA and have a concern about our processing of personal information that we are not able to resolve, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the data privacy authority where you reside.  For contact details of your local Data Protection Authority, please see: <http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/article-29/structure/data-protection-authorities/index_en.htm>.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the “last updated” date at the top of this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you check our website from time to time to inform yourself of any changes in this Privacy Policy or any of our other policies.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or comments regarding our privacy practices or this Privacy Policy, you may  contact us at:

C-Change Media, Inc.  
101 Broadway, Suite 208  
Oakland, CA 94607

Or by emailing our [General Manager](mailto:heather@poetsandquants.com).

_Effective Date: May 25, 2018_
